antioch.edu 2019-08-08

# Privacy Policy | Antioch University

Antioch University (“Antioch”) takes online privacy and security seriously. Following is a summary of Antioch’s security and privacy policies and procedures relating to website visitors and users. By using Antioch’s website, you signify that you have read these terms and agree to be bound by and comply with them.

A.  Data Security

Antioch has put in place appropriate physical, electronic, and managerial procedures to prevent unauthorized access to, and ensure the correct use of, information that we collect online. For more information regarding Antioch’s data security practices, please see the Information Security Policy 8.105 and the Student Records (FERPA) Policy 5.629.

B.  Passive User Data Collection and Use

Like other web service providers, Antioch may track user browsing patterns to increase understanding of how our websites are used. We may share non-identifying and aggregate information with third-party partners to the extent necessary to improve our web services or better communicate with users. We may also collect information such as IP addresses of website visitors and place cookies on visitors’ devices. Antioch uses the following types of cookies:

  1. Necessary. Necessary cookies are required to enable core site functionality. They are necessary for a visitor to utilize the websites and therefore do not require consent.
  2. Functional. Functional cookies allow Antioch to analyze site usage in order to measure and improve performance. You may configure your browser settings to refuse the use of cookies; however, doing so may affect some aspects of website functionality. Antioch uses Google Analytics, which may place cookies on users’ devices and/or collect the Internet protocol (IP) address of website visitors to track website usage data. Google Analytics collects information anonymously and reports website trends without identifying individual visitors. Antioch uses the information collected to understand how our visitors are using the websites and make improvements for a better online experience.Antioch does not use Google Analytics to track or collect personal information and we do not associate personal information with web analytics information. The Google Analytics privacy policy is available at: <http://www.google.com/intl/en/analytics/privacyoverview.html> and the Google Analytics Opt Out is available at: <https://support.google.com/analytics/answer/181881?hl=en>.
  3. Advertising. Advertising cookies are placed by advertising companies to provide ads that are relevant to user interests. You may configure your browser settings to refuse the use of cookies; however, doing so may affect some aspects of website functionality.

C.  Active User Data Collection and Use

Should you voluntarily provide Antioch with personal information through website forms, Antioch will not share, sell, rent, trade, or authorize any third party to use your personal information for the purpose of commercial gain without your permission.

Antioch may use any email address, phone number or mailing address you provide to send you information, respond to inquiries, and/or other requests or questions.

Antioch may use your personal information to process student, financial aid or job applications, student or employee registrations, and other transactions, services and benefits that we provide to our students, employees and other persons.

Antioch may share personal information with third-party partners to the extent necessary for such third parties to provide services to Antioch, our students, employees and other persons. Any third parties who receive user information for this purpose are prohibited from using or sharing user information for any other purpose.

Antioch reserves the right to provide your information to third parties when required by applicable law, regulation, legal process or governmental request; to detect or prevent fraud, security or technical issues; or to protect the rights, property or safety of Antioch, our users or others.

D.  Questions, Concerns and How to Opt Out.

Please submit questions and concerns about the Antioch website to [AUwebmaster@antioch.edu](mailto:AUwebmaster@antioch.edu).

If you have provided consent to the use of your information, you have the right to withdraw consent at any time by contacting [AUwebmaster@antioch.edu](mailto:AUwebmaster@antioch.edu). You may have the right to request access to, a copy of, correction, restriction in the use of, or erasure of your information, depending upon where the information originated.

If you feel that Antioch has not complied with applicable foreign laws regulating user information, you have the right to file a complaint with the appropriate supervisory authority in the European Union.

E.  Policy Changes

Antioch may update or change this policy at any time. Your continued use of this site after any such change indicates your acceptance of the changes.
